Do y'all even know what APAC is?
Or is it just something you've heard mentioned?
Because I'm beginning to think that you don't actually know what APAC is.
And I'm willing to explain.
But I get the feeling that a lot of people don't actually know what APAC is.
And thus, they don't seem to grasp how it's all connected.
And I think that's because when I talk about, there is no Philly date yet.
When I talk about Zio's, it's like people don't understand the connection between APAC and Zio's.
And I feel like people heard Charlemagne and others say, don't support politicians accepting APAC.
But then they don't know why.
Like, and that was never stated.
It was never stated why you shouldn't support politicians taking money from APAC.
So, okay, yeah, no.
Okay, okay.
APAC is one of several Israel lobbying groups.
Do we know what a lobbying group is?
Let's start there.
Why are you worried about what the blue light is in the corner?
What does that have to do with you?
Okay.
All right.
So some people in here don't know what a lobbying group is.
So I will explain.
A lobbying group is a group that literally goes to members of Congress
to make requests on behalf of corporations and organizations.
I say corporations and organizations because they also make requests on behalf of nonprofits.
And for those who don't realize, nonprofits are the corporate wing of basically the monetizing of harm.
Okay.
So when we're talking about lobbying groups, they are literally salespeople who are conferring with politicians
to get certain legislation passed or not passed in order to increase the efficacy or the goals of a particular company.
And yes, A.O. Prince, it is corruption.
Now, this also is beyond companies, but it's actual sectors.
So you have the insurance sector.
You have the private sector.
You have the oil and gas and fossil fuel sector.
You have the transportation sector, etc.
So you have all of these different spaces that have been deeply privatized
that are getting representation via money on the Hill.
And so they literally go to meet with these people and they barter.
We'll give you this if you give us this.
We'll do this if you do this.
They are the bureaucrats that are interacting and that you don't have.
You don't have people that are doing that for you, but companies have people doing that for them.
Sectors have people doing that for them.
And then it goes to a whole other level where it's beyond lobbyists.
And it is direct money that is being spent, put in pockets of not just politicians,
but also of the Supreme Court in order to get certain things passed or certain things moved off the table
or certain limitations, right?
Like certain, why can't I think of the word?
But basically, like when you see recently, the EPA has removed,
has removed bans on certain chemicals.
So now those chemicals can now be put back into the marketplace and it allows for a company to be able to do that.
Now, that is lobbying.
Does everyone understand now what lobbying is?
Because I won't move on until you tell me.
If you need me to say more, I will say more.
Okay.
So folks follow what lobbying is.
Now, so someone said, say more.
So we now in the United States have expanded the power of corporations by identifying them as individuals, as people,
because there were limitations on how corporations could involve themselves in elections.
So it went from just being able to interact with elected officials to also being able to interact with unelected officials
and saying, we will thus give you this if you will promise us, et cetera, et cetera, et cetera, once you get in office.
So when we are seeing these PACs, right, political action committees, they are monies, they are basically campaign corporations.
They are collecting money from donors and you do not necessarily see who they have collected money from.
Okay.
They have collected money from donors and that money is then given to an elected, I mean, given to a official that is running for office as a donation.
But what it allows for is allows for there to be a blanket of secrecy over where the money is coming from.
And this allows for there to be a more difficult process for people to be able to see how the people they're voting for are being supported.
So when we talk about the Israel lobby, what we're talking about is PACs that are funded by Zionists to create legislative strengths for the state of Israel and its supporters.
So if we're going to connect all those dots, we know that there are aspects associated with the state of Israel that are absolutely harmful to not only USCans, but to the globe.
Largely in part because Zionists are very deeply embedded in a number of all of these sectors that we have discussed.
Many of these sectors are also incredibly implicit, complicit in climate change, right?
They are complicit in health care limitations.
They are complicit in law enforcement and the way that's carried out.
They are complicit in privatization, etc.
We know that Zionism is a settler colonial practice.
It is a political settler colonial ideology.
And if you understand settler colonialism, its goal is to take and spread.
Take and spread.
That is the goal of settler colonialism.
We have seen settler colonialism in the British Empire.
We have seen settler colonialism in the Belgium Empire.
We have seen settler colonialism in the French and Spanish empires and Japanese.
In the current neocolonialism, we have seen in the United States, right?
We know that the United States has colonies.
The Virgin Islands is a United States colony.
Puerto Rico is a United States colony.
Guam is a United States colony.
Hawaii is a United States colony, okay?
Settler colonialism's goal is world domination.
That is the goal of settler colonialism.
The procurement of territory and resources by any means.
The United States has completely committed itself to this for the last 60 years on a very soft power and hard power level.
However, Zayos have been surreptitiously setting the stage for their own expansion as well.
The Israeli lobby includes AIPAC.
AIPAC's effort is to advance settler colonialism.
Now, at 9 o'clock tonight, Donald Trump is supposedly going to be announcing war with Venezuela.
So right now, there is a very cohesive relationship between Zayos and the United States in their goal of settler colonialism.
And this is making individuals get rich.
AIPAC is just one of several Israel lobbies that uses American legislators to put money in the pockets of Zayos
and to help advance the interests of Israeli settler colonialism.
Are y'all following me?
So when we talk about why is it not okay for politicians to make money from AIPAC, to take money from AIPAC,
it is because they are actively supporting the efforts of the Israeli lobby to harm the world.
And in this current iteration, by using U.S. taxpayer dollars to do so.
This is not simply a Palestine issue.
There are other lobbies that do this same work.
There's J Street.
I can't remember some of the names off top, but you can Google them.
And let me also state that these lobbies have other organizations attached to them.
For instance, Jasmine Crockett says, I did not take AIPAC money.
However, she did take money from an organization that on its website refers to itself as the foundation associated with AIPAC.
It is literally their foundation arm.
When you see someone like James Tallarico say, I'm not taking money from AIPAC.
This has simply just become a buzz phrase to get you all to stop paying attention because AIPAC has now had a light shined on it.
But that doesn't change the fact that there is still incredible danger in taking money from Zionists because it advances the settler colonial interests that harm you.
So when you have James Tallarico say, I am not taking money from AIPAC while not actively, while not concretely stating, I am not taking money from Miriam Adelson, who we know is a Zion billionaire that funds both Democrats and Republicans.
We understand that he is still taking money from Americans, we understand that he is still taking Zio money.
Also, if you ask me what's the solution, I will block you.
If you ask me what's the solution, I will block you.
So just know that.
You get one, if you ask me, so I've said it now.
If you ask me what's the solution, I will block you.
It is a disingenuous question, and I'm no longer going to engage with it because it is actually nonsense.
Let me also add that there is something very disingenuous about anyone stating Israel has the right to defend itself.
Israel does not have the right to defend itself when it is the offender.
Remember, when you are actively being the offense and you are creating all of the acrimony and the violence in your region, you are not the one in defense.
You are the one in offense.
So there is a consistent misplacement of actual legitimacy when that statement is made.
It is also Hasbara.
That is Zio public relations.
Okay?
Now, I don't know, Steve, why you're saying we need Jasmine Crockett.
I don't know what Jasmine Crockett has done that is so effective that you would say that you need her.
Or I guess maybe you're being facetious, SVP.
Because ultimately, anyone who states, I will take money from these people who I know to be harmful is not going to be a useful tool for change.
Period.
This is not subjective.
This is not opinion.
This is a fact.
So when I see James Tallarico completely word salad-ing the very direct question that was asked of him, which was, are you going to be taking money from Muriel Adelson?
While also doing a very threading of the needle tactic and saying, we should not be supporting Benjamin Netanyahu and we should not be supporting the harm of Palestinians.
While also saying Israel has the right to defend itself while any other country, as any other country does, you are literally watching somebody talk out two sides of their neck.
The country of Israel is a nation-state born from theft and violence.
It is also deeply embroiled in the disruption, violence, and the starvation of folks all across this world.
So to suggest that it is only a Palestine issue is simply not genuine.
It is also involved in the Congo.
It is also involved in Sudan.
It is also involved in Guatemala.
And its artillery is also all over the world because artillery is not simply just at this point.
It's not simply just weapons.
It is surveillance.
And all of the actual practice that they have done with surveillance on the Palestinians is now being exported to the world.
So I see people say, well, what are we going to do?
And I don't think people really understand the dynamics of politics, which is that these people require you to be in power.
And in order for them to be placed in power, you have to give them that ability.
When you vote, you are voting as if you have confidence in them.
So when I see people still engaging in the voting, it says to them, we still believe in you.
Their only path to success is you.
I don't think folks really grasp that because folks say, well, if we don't vote, somebody is going to get put in office.
Well, if you don't vote effectively, then you're still not going to have the right person in office.
So if you don't actively use your vote as something with power, then it's still going to end up the same way.
I never used to believe in the concept of holding the vote until I understood that the dynamic is not we hoping for them.
It's them hoping for us.
So this idea of, oh, if we just vote, that's enough, is honestly you showing up consistently to say, I am giving confidence to these people, even though they don't deserve it.
I would like to make it abundantly clear that just saying APAC is not enough because it does not address the complete complicity
of all Zio monies and organizations in the global repression of anybody who is not them.
I need to really make that clear to you because I don't think people understand that APAC is supporting of apartheid.
It supports Jewish supremacy under the guise of Zionists.
Because if you don't support Zionism, even if you are Jewish, then they do not support you.
So it is apartheid.
Apartheid is the system of separation based on ethnicity.
We are watching apartheid happen in real time in this era right now.
I'm not yelling at you.
I speak loud.
That's part of my autism.
We are watching apartheid in real time in this nation right now, even just on the sheer basis that you are seeing Zios get treated explicitly different by the Justice Department, by the police, etc., than folks who are challenging them.
So when we are actively watching First Amendment rights of U.S. citizens be completely dismantled for speaking against another country or speaking against use of money being used in genocide,
while we are actively watching the support of a genocide, we're actively watching individuals who have been involved in pedophilia be exported back to Israel where they can be safe.
We are actively watching individuals who are stealing people's homes.
Go take a look at what's going on in New York.
They are stealing people's homes.
And I don't mean in the West Bank, even though they're doing that as well.
They're doing that here in the United States.
They are stealing people's homes.
So we do not control.
OK, someone here is saying we control who gets voted as president.
I have no idea why you think we control who gets voted as president.
I just for the life of me can't understand why you think that's the case.
We do not control who gets voted as president, not overtly or covertly.
There's an entire electoral college that is in the way of that.
Furthermore, the United States is complicit and explicit in its intervening of democratic elections and its overthrowing of democratic elections on a regular basis.
It's literally doing it right now in Honduras, in Honduras right now.
And yet folks think that it is somehow giving fair elections to the United States like that doesn't make any sense.
I've never understood.
Yes, Al Gore is an example.
And it is not by happenstance that two current members of the Supreme Court were a part of the legal team that overthrew the election of Al Gore and gave it to George Bush.
And they took Al Gore in a room and Al Gore came out and said, OK, fine, concede.
So when we come back around to the beginning of the conversation and what is APAC, APAC is not the be all end all.
And that's really what the reason was I wanted to come on here is to really give you a greater context of the fact that APAC is simply just the name and lights of a much deeper and darker web of money that is supporting a political ideology.
That seeks to create supremacy on a global level that currently exists in Israel.
So I will say that one more time.
APAC is the beacon.
For a much broader and deeper network of money that supports the expansion of the political ideology grounded in supremacy that is currently in power in existence in Israel and exporting it to the globe.
I hope this helps.
Have a good night, y'all.